orange.com 2013-09-10

# privacy policy

This Privacy Policy explains how Orange SA (“Orange”) uses, shares and protects your personal information and is applicable to this Site. By accessing, browsing and/or using the Site you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

## 1\. your information

By subscribing to all or part of publications  of Orange, you consent to receive such publication(s) that may include information in relation to products and services which Orange considers may be of interest to you. Orange will not share your email address with third parties.  
If you have any questions about the handling or protection of your personal data, please contact the orange.com  manager at [infos.groupe@orange.com](mailto:infos.groupe@orange.com)

## 2\. supply and accuracy of information

When you provide to Orange any information, you undertake to notify Orange of any changes to the information which you provide from time to time. You have a right to ask for a copy of your information (for which Orange will charge a small fee) and to correct any inaccuracies in it.

## 3\. disclosure of your information to third parties

Orange may disclose your personal data acting in good faith if it believes that such action is necessary to: (i) conform with a legal requirement; or (ii) comply with a legal process; or (iii) defend the rights or property of Orange.

## 4\. cookies

A cookie is a small text file sent by a web server when you visit a website and that is stored by your web browser’s device (pc or other); so that it can later be read back from that browser. Cookies may store your preferences and other information but will not identify you as an individual. Orange uses cookies to provide, for the purposes of Orange internal usage only, some audience statistics in relation with the Site. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser  (*) setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you chose to decline cookies some of the interactive features of this Site may not be available to you. Orange is committed to protecting your privacy and only uses cookies to improve the performance of the Site to you. The usage patterns tracked by cookies remain confidential and Orange does not share or sell any cookie-generated information with third parties .

## customers in United Kingdom

## 5\. minors

No information should be submitted to the Site by persons under the age of 18 years.

## 6\. change

Orange reserves the right to vary the terms of this Privacy Policy from time to time, such variations becoming effective immediately upon posting of the varied Privacy Policy on the Site. You will be deemed to accept the updated Privacy Policy available on the Site, each time you access to or use the Site.

This Privacy Policy shall be governed and construed in accordance with the laws of France and you and Orange agree to submit to the jurisdiction of the courts of Paris, France, over any claim or matter arising under or in connection with this Privacy Policy.

© 2012 Orange  
Last update: 2012, December, 4th

last update: 24 June 2013
